Guide to the Family Life Development Center records, 1974-2010.
Family Life Development Center records, 1974-2010
- Series VI: The Military Projects
  - New Parent Support Programs in the Military Services Report for the Dept. of Defense, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Drill Sergeant Spouse Seminar Participant Handbook and Seven Tips to Courtesies and Protocol: What Army Spouses Need to Know, 2008 (Box 27)
  - Rape and Sexual Assault Training U.S. Marine Corps Family Advocacy Program, Undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Family Advocacy Program Case Review Committee Practices and Procedures Final Report, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Command Briefing Materials Department of Defense Healthy Parenting Initiative, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Army Commander's Guide to Family Readiness Group Operation, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Department of the Army Support for Families Hearts Apart, 2007, 2012 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Army Care Team Handbook, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Army Leader's Handbook Trauma in the Unit, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Army Family Readiness Group Leader's Handbook, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Drill Sergeant Spouse Seminar Participant Handbook and Seven Tips to Courtesies and Protocol: What Army Spouses Need to Know, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Drill Sergent Spouse Seminar Facilator's Guide, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Inter-service Family Assistance Committee Resource Guide, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Family Advocacy Prevention and Treatment within an Extraordinary Army Conference Report, 2009-08-09-2009-08-14 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Brochures, Undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Army Family Advocacy Program Commander's Guide, Undated; CD-3559
  - Army Family Advocacy Program Commander's Guide: Printer's Files, Undated; CD-3560
  - Command Briefing Materials Department of Defense Healthy Parenting Initiative, 2002; CD-3561
  - Army New Parent Support Program, 2006; CD-3562
  - Army Operation Ready Materials, 2007-06; CD-3563
  - Army Support for Families Heartsapart, 2007; CD-3564
  - Army Operation Ready Materials Training Resources for Trauma in the Unit Care Teams, 2007; CD-3565
  - Army Drill Sergeant Spouse Seminar Facilitator's Guide, 2008; CD-3566
  - Army Family Advocacy Program Emergency Placement Care Resource Manual, Undated; CD-3567
  - Army Family Readiness Support Assistant Resource Guide, Undated; CD-3568
- Series VII: Dolls Used in Counseling Sessions
  - Dolls (Box 4)
  - Dolls (Box 5)
- Series VIII: Conferences and Presentations
  - The Immigrant Child: Past, Present & Future: leaflet, 2008; DVD-506-512 (Box 23)
  - A. Iscol Family Program for Leadership Development in Public Service
  - Adolescents and War: How Youth Deal with Political Violence-Dr. Brian Barber, 2007-12-05; DVD-610
  - Is Development Possible Today? -Christopher London, 2006-11-14; DVD-613
  - New Unionism: Delivering the Promise of a Fair Economy -Sara Horowitz, 2008-09-08; DVD-614
  - Education for Social Justice: El Puente -Luis Garden Acosta and Frances Lucerna, 2002-09-25; DVD-615
  - A Harder Thing: Discovering My Work in East Harlem -Ivan Hageman, 2003-09-24; DVD-616
  - The Light of Conscience: How A Simple Act Can Change Your Life -Bill Shore, 2004-09-14; DVD-617
  - "Someday You'll Change the World...Welcome to Someday" -Dr. Ken Grouf, 2005-09-20; DVD-618
  - "Me to We: Finding Meaning in a Material World" -Craig Kielburger, 2007-10-10; DVD-619
  - Reforming Public Education:How to Change the Conversation -Michelle Rhee, 2009-10-05; DVD-620
  - Bridging the Gap Between Rich and Poor in an Interconnected World -Jacqueline Novogratz, 2010-09-27; DVD-621
  - B. John Doris Lectures
  - 5 Decades Since Publication of the "Battered Child Syndrome":Lessons Learned about Child Maltreatment-Dr. John Leventhal, 2008-04-10; DVD-611
  - Nurse-Family Partnership: From Trials to International Replication -David Olds, 2009-12-07; DVD-612
  - The Effects of Early Experience:Illustrations from a Multi-Level Perspective on Child Maltreatment-Dr. Dante Cicchetti, 2010-04-22; DVD-622